I only when it comes to their health insurance, a lot of
senior citizens like you, oh all health
insurance should be taken elastic, I had made a video on the
question turn thing plan with the intention of looting from I had made a video on it
and shared it with you
earlier,
you will find the links of both these videos
in the description box, the
method of some time before morning, its quantity, which
according to today's time, some plans
are available for senior students, they should be given a comeback,
you give balance for you, we are adding
I C of potential and lemon on
senior Scotland from both sides,
what is the difference, what are the similarities, cost is
required and what is there for you, it will keep playing,
before starting the video, request reminder, if you have
not yet subscribed to my channel,
subscribe, then decide information
entry like, let's move towards the video,
I advised Golden Shuaib, on lemon, you
can do less for seniors, first of all we will
talk about the claim settlement
rates of both frustrated countries  IS A
Romantic
93.08
is the death
that it is,
subscribe
and subscribe to this channel,
you will get it in both the companies, you can
take it by the means that
we can make a minimum entry of 216 years in the first year
and a maximum entry of seventy five years,
now
monsoon vendor in both the polythenes, this is a
lifetime continuation, till you are told why,
we can renew our policy, if we
talk about the policy then there
is a back of 121 seniors moments,
in both the pilots, you know, you can make a long term
deposit, either the company gives you its glue,
you will decide the premium for 2 years or 3 years in front,
then we will see some work for ourselves, you will
talk about room rent,
IS A non by gold lying on the table in the room, when she attends
Smith below you and there is a
friend on gas, always above lakh, so
single private and fruit, lemon sweat can be
25 in the purse, if he takes platinum round
policy, then here you will see the
print  The style that you get, if you want to
take a policy then you will
get this credit in Sindhu's natural form,
see I comment on the stairs of both the
policies of Congress, there is a hospitalization
notification that you are at home, click here
and it is not certain that you can get
admitted in the hospital, you will get it in the hospital
and the treatment of considered S is
yours, that notification Gehlot
kilometer hospitalization is
converted in both the quality, subscribe to S A real
man, then there is a little difference in both,
like IT Bob Houghton has ID
verification balance, if you have different glass then you can get
unlimited number of times of distress,
you can always back up
if you have tempered glass, then once you get
half a lemon on the platform, to deal with the alarm in serials, you can
meet the same person for any treatment, for any disease,
you can get any treatment,
unlimited number of sciences of people can be done,
so there is no infection here, now
Priyanka will keep coming to hospitalization, that
means hospital, first there is one sciences and
after Sector-16 there is another and one  Its
population introduction of both polytechnics the
money Arora will get on decisions golden
changemakers scent of mist
maximum from z tube that this decision
is hospitalization on Twenty20 this will
talk about movement 80%
power 2.5 lakh
no claim bonus no claim
bonus will go up to maximum
in the policy of help from both sides
and if there is any in it then it will
not be reduced no claim bonus in both
share it as
well as there is such fold fold click on subscribe button on this side
and
like
share and
subscribe to my channel to
qualification which is called alternative treatment
ayurvedic and unani siddha and
homeopathy this cloth
is absolutely hospitalization in it illegal take now
200 MB mental balance at song from 2010
which is available in your policy such number
your answer list is available in balance sheet
and minimum on serials 500 to
1000 and 500 policy two and a half thousand rupees and
mixing ₹10 if we talk about balance then there
was tie from getting it note  Unleashed
Hand Tak is a share management program for which you can
refer your real video of these to the High Court bench. There is no
such hard side effect available in Lemon Pass. The
mobile
application of this number is Take Care Mobile
Application. Lemon Pass is there, so you
can download both the mobile applications
and can manage your policy very well. The
dose you drink at both the times is
nothing on the room. The team from the ID
in the mobile phone screen, Rewa Quote 380 minimum,
both are quoted in this purse. Payment option,
so there is a co payment option in the quantity of both.
Little wider audience, in this minimum co
payment 20%, they can use you notification. Thirty
percent positive person or 50%,
your PIN number will be dialed. Lemon
in Senior Purse 2030 50%, then curd will
definitely give the payment option along with the choice. If you want to choose
not to co payment now if you
want comprehensive coverage then that is
also available here. Doctor option
is available in both. Special friendly eye  You will get back to build your family on the
fifth semester. You will take 20%
off Baroda deductible. On top of that,
select the polythene which comes from any ATM. Then
with dal-rice, you will see that the film
reduces a lot. For example, if
you have already taken 10 lakh rupees, then you will get a
person force of Tubelight. And on
top of that, you will see ₹1000000 half an hour supreme.
If I will definitely share with you, there is a
huge difference in payment
with zero percent payment notification
because the company is not going to have any problem in the market.
If you make your
policy in front of this question
and make it thick, then 2.5 percent additional is the
account. There
is a discount in ILO magnesium in hanging fasting. High
tide discount. If you have taken an examination for
Namo for Philippines, then
you will get 2.5 likes. Here you will bring to the front. We will
talk about optional color. In IS A node
special, there is optional palace in protractor
so that ultimately not tenable item gets ridden.  There are
151 options which we talked about that
whenever you can choose there is notification for
payment option, you can modify it by getting it,
friend 9:00 program we saw that
balance is left, in the same way there is national that
care personal problem, you can pop it
if you need and animal or purse
side, in this way I have these
things that prove to be your marketable
items, secondly if your
according to it then no claim bonus love on
your eyes, thirdly your
support according to inflation, smart engine c
insulating is serious, in both the policies
this is the meeting's judgment in these, both are
already set and generation best loading, there is
Bharatiya
Jan Sangh, there is no loading on them, there is
polish on both, there are some APS due to which there is
no loading, which means your peppermint is
not free, which increases in the policies,
specifications are just
related to this, so it was that there was
another increase rate hand in the number golden saree, which
you can have for diabetes, hypertension and heart
related diseases, there is no such specific
playlist just like this lemon  Senior
can do it now we will see pre-menopause
till success we need to track so for free
I have taken one here public 1606
so treatment could have been done if husband comes
he will be saved I take LIC policy with separate 20%
payment so from I number
golden only Kim points 157 Saudi
90% tasty Sapphire and senior category result is
535 time positive like definitely like
permit no report nothing to take
other person insurance company will give
that option right now IS A name of water left
is not available in lemon pass India pass
its result will come in 607 third option is
absolutely with your talent policy
and wall paint Balua Tola Gopi so let's
describe the decisions there will be a change in style you a
loved one minimum premium for seniors
is 2455 so apply here for quacks it is
less than five if you send them then their
leg can be amputated I will give you this just
remember it is important to comment from me
which one you have  Teacher in his policy
and secondly I would like to tell you free call
free medical checkup camp reply
what is medical checkup the medical test before taking the policy
I call it bring
positive medical checkup exam date
if we talk in today's date then you can do it
in mobile only five please policy
medical checkup for this policy you can do it for
low quality
150 seats in it there is no test from the policy
this note policy medical checkup is what
you will fill my application you will fill the proposal form on the
basis of that there is one thing inside that
you have such so this difference between is a
boy who turns leader lever back lever
crop tell me which next video you
want to see and what you want to do some
questions on land guarantee city comment
section you can digitally give us whatsapp number or
any
reminder before if you have not subscribed to my channel yet
subscribe
on Sudha's website we get agri guide sends
quick stakes so Prem comes to MNREGA bank
po
towards the video and
loot to
maximum yash and mej number  The
policy of Rs 5 lakh is fixed,
both have tried